<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<?metadataRepository version='1.2.0'?>
<repository name='update site: https://testng.org/testng-eclipse-update-site/updatesites/6.11.0.201703011520' type='org.eclipse.equinox.internal.p2.metadata.repository.LocalMetadataRepository' version='1'>
  <properties size='2'>
    <property name='p2.timestamp' value='1666177266861'/>
    <property name='site.checksum' value='1980967843'/>
  </properties>
  <units size='7'>
    <unit id='org.testng.eclipse.feature.jar' version='6.11.0.201703011520'>
      <properties size='4'>
        <property name='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.name' value='TestNG'/>
        <property name='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.description' value='TestNG plug-in for Eclipse.'/>
        <property name='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.description.url' value='http://testng.org'/>
        <property name='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.provider' value='Cedric Beust'/>
      </properties>
      <provides size='3'>
        <provided namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.iu' name='org.testng.eclipse.feature.jar' version='6.11.0.201703011520'/>
        <provided namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.eclipse.type' name='feature' version='1.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='org.eclipse.update.feature' name='org.testng.eclipse' version='6.11.0.201703011520'/>
      </provides>
      <filter>
        (org.eclipse.update.install.features=true)
      </filter>
      <artifacts size='1'>
        <artifact classifier='org.eclipse.update.feature' id='org.testng.eclipse' version='6.11.0.201703011520'/>
      </artifacts>
      <touchpoint id='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.osgi' version='1.0.0'/>
      <touchpointData size='1'>
        <instructions size='1'>
          <instruction key='zipped'>
            true
          </instruction>
        </instructions>
      </touchpointData>
      <licenses size='1'>
        <license uri='http://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0.html' url='http://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0.html'>
          Apache License&#xA;Version 2.0, January 2004&#xA;http://www.apache.org/licenses/&#xA;TERMS AND CONDITIONS FOR USE, REPRODUCTION, AND DISTRIBUTION&#xA;1. Definitions.&#xA;&quot;License&quot; shall mean the terms and conditions for use, reproduction,&#xA;and distribution as defined by Sections 1 through 9 of this document.&#xA;&quot;Licensor&quot; shall mean the copyright owner or entity authorized&#xA;by the copyright owner that is granting the License.&#xA;&quot;Legal Entity&quot; shall mean the union of the acting entity and&#xA;all other entities that control, are controlled by, or are under&#xA;common control with that entity. For the purposes of this definition,&#xA;&quot;control&quot; means (i) the power, direct or indirect, to cause the&#xA;direction or management of such entity, whether by contract or&#xA;otherwise, or (ii) ownership of fifty percent (50%) or more of&#xA;the outstanding shares, or (iii) beneficial ownership of such&#xA;entity.&#xA;&quot;You&quot; (or &quot;Your&quot;) shall mean an individual or Legal Entity exercising&#xA;permissions granted by this License.&#xA;&quot;Source&quot; form shall mean the preferred form for making modifications,&#xA;including but not limited to software source code, documentation&#xA;source, and configuration files.&#xA;&quot;Object&quot; form shall mean any form resulting from mechanical transformation&#xA;or translation of a Source form, including but not limited to&#xA;compiled object code, generated documentation, and conversions&#xA;to other media types.&#xA;&quot;Work&quot; shall mean the work of authorship, whether in Source or&#xA;Object form, made available under the License, as indicated by&#xA;a copyright notice that is included in or attached to the work&#xA;(an example is provided in the Appendix below).&#xA;&quot;Derivative Works&quot; shall mean any work, whether in Source or&#xA;Object form, that is based on (or derived from) the Work and&#xA;for which the editorial revisions, annotations, elaborations,&#xA;or other modifications represent, as a whole, an original work&#xA;of authorship. For the purposes of this License, Derivative Works&#xA;shall not include works that remain separable from, or merely&#xA;link (or bind by name) to the interfaces of, the Work and Derivative&#xA;Works thereof.&#xA;&quot;Contribution&quot; shall mean any work of authorship, including the&#xA;original version of the Work and any modifications or additions&#xA;to that Work or Derivative Works thereof, that is intentionally&#xA;submitted to Licensor for inclusion in the Work by the copyright&#xA;owner or by an individual or Legal Entity authorized to submit&#xA;on behalf of the copyright owner. For the purposes of this definition,&#xA;&quot;submitted&quot; means any form of electronic, verbal, or written&#xA;communication sent to the Licensor or its representatives, including&#xA;but not limited to communication on electronic mailing lists,&#xA;source code control systems, and issue tracking systems that&#xA;are managed by, or on behalf of, the Licensor for the purpose&#xA;of discussing and improving the Work, but excluding communication&#xA;that is conspicuously marked or otherwise designated in writing&#xA;by the copyright owner as &quot;Not a Contribution.&quot;&#xA;&quot;Contributor&quot; shall mean Licensor and any individual or Legal&#xA;Entity on behalf of whom a Contribution has been received by&#xA;Licensor and subsequently incorporated within the Work.&#xA;2. Grant of Copyright License. Subject to the terms and conditions&#xA;of this License, each Contributor hereby grants to You a perpetual,&#xA;worldwide, non-exclusive, no-charge, royalty-free, irrevocable&#xA;copyright license to reproduce, prepare Derivative Works of,&#xA;publicly display, publicly perform, sublicense, and distribute&#xA;the Work and such Derivative Works in Source or Object form.&#xA;3. Grant of Patent License. Subject to the terms and conditions&#xA;of this License, each Contributor hereby grants to You a perpetual,&#xA;worldwide, non-exclusive, no-charge, royalty-free, irrevocable&#xA;(except as stated in this section) patent license to make, have&#xA;made, use, offer to sell, sell, import, and otherwise transfer&#xA;the Work, where such license applies only to those patent claims&#xA;licensable by such Contributor that are necessarily infringed&#xA;by their Contribution(s) alone or by combination of their Contribution(s)&#xA;with the Work to which such Contribution(s) was submitted. If&#xA;You institute patent litigation against any entity (including&#xA;a cross-claim or counterclaim in a lawsuit) alleging that the&#xA;Work or a Contribution incorporated within the Work constitutes&#xA;direct or contributory patent infringement, then any patent licenses&#xA;granted to You under this License for that Work shall terminate&#xA;as of the date such litigation is filed.&#xA;4. Redistribution. You may reproduce and distribute copies of&#xA;the Work or Derivative Works thereof in any medium, with or without&#xA;modifications, and in Source or Object form, provided that You&#xA;meet the following conditions:&#xA;1. You must give any other recipients of the Work or Derivative&#xA;Works a copy of this License; and&#xA;2. You must cause any modified files to carry prominent notices&#xA;stating that You changed the files; and&#xA;3. You must retain, in the Source form of any Derivative Works&#xA;that You distribute, all copyright, patent, trademark, and attribution&#xA;notices from the Source form of the Work, excluding those notices&#xA;that do not pertain to any part of the Derivative Works; and&#xA;4. If the Work includes a &quot;NOTICE&quot; text file as part of its distribution,&#xA;then any Derivative Works that You distribute must include a&#xA;readable copy of the attribution notices contained within such&#xA;NOTICE file, excluding those notices that do not pertain to any&#xA;part of the Derivative Works, in at least one of the following&#xA;places: within a NOTICE text file distributed as part of the&#xA;Derivative Works; within the Source form or documentation, if&#xA;provided along with the Derivative Works; or, within a display&#xA;generated by the Derivative Works, if and wherever such third-party&#xA;notices normally appear. The contents of the NOTICE file are&#xA;for informational purposes only and do not modify the License.&#xA;You may add Your own attribution notices within Derivative Works&#xA;that You distribute, alongside or as an addendum to the NOTICE&#xA;text from the Work, provided that such additional attribution&#xA;notices cannot be construed as modifying the License.&#xA;You may add Your own copyright statement to Your modifications&#xA;and may provide additional or different license terms and conditions&#xA;for use, reproduction, or distribution of Your modifications,&#xA;or for any such Derivative Works as a whole, provided Your use,&#xA;reproduction, and distribution of the Work otherwise complies&#xA;with the conditions stated in this License.&#xA;5. Submission of Contributions. Unless You explicitly state otherwise,&#xA;any Contribution intentionally submitted for inclusion in the&#xA;Work by You to the Licensor shall be under the terms and conditions&#xA;of this License, without any additional terms or conditions.&#xA;Notwithstanding the above, nothing herein shall supersede or&#xA;modify the terms of any separate license agreement you may have&#xA;executed with Licensor regarding such Contributions.&#xA;6. Trademarks. This License does not grant permission to use&#xA;the trade names, trademarks, service marks, or product names&#xA;of the Licensor, except as required for reasonable and customary&#xA;use in describing the origin of the Work and reproducing the&#xA;content of the NOTICE file.&#xA;7. Disclaimer of Warranty. Unless required by applicable law&#xA;or agreed to in writing, Licensor provides the Work (and each&#xA;Contributor provides its Contributions) on an &quot;AS IS&quot; BASIS,&#xA;WITHOUT WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF ANY KIND, either express&#xA;or implied, including, without limitation, any warranties or&#xA;conditions of TITLE, NON-INFRINGEMENT, MERCHANTABILITY, or FITNESS&#xA;FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE. You are solely responsible for determining&#xA;the appropriateness of using or redistributing the Work and assume&#xA;any risks associated with Your exercise of permissions under&#xA;this License.&#xA;8. Limitation of Liability. In no event and under no legal theory,&#xA;whether in tort (including negligence), contract, or otherwise,&#xA;unless required by applicable law (such as deliberate and grossly&#xA;negligent acts) or agreed to in writing, shall any Contributor&#xA;be liable to You for damages, including any direct, indirect,&#xA;special, incidental, or consequential damages of any character&#xA;arising as a result of this License or out of the use or inability&#xA;to use the Work (including but not limited to damages for loss&#xA;of goodwill, work stoppage, computer failure or malfunction,&#xA;or any and all other commercial damages or losses), even if such&#xA;Contributor has been advised of the possibility of such damages.&#xA;9. Accepting Warranty or Additional Liability. While redistributing&#xA;the Work or Derivative Works thereof, You may choose to offer,&#xA;and charge a fee for, acceptance of support, warranty, indemnity,&#xA;or other liability obligations and/or rights consistent with&#xA;this License. However, in accepting such obligations, You may&#xA;act only on Your own behalf and on Your sole responsibility,&#xA;not on behalf of any other Contributor, and only if You agree&#xA;to indemnify, defend, and hold each Contributor harmless for&#xA;any liability incurred by, or claims asserted against, such Contributor&#xA;by reason of your accepting any such warranty or additional liability.&#xA;END OF TERMS AND CONDITIONS
        </license>
      </licenses>
      <copyright uri='http://beust.com' url='http://beust.com'>
        Copyright 2004-2016 Cedric Beust.
      </copyright>
    </unit>
    <unit id='org.testng.eclipse.feature.group' version='6.11.0.201703011520' singleton='false'>
      <update id='org.testng.eclipse.feature.group' range='[0.0.0,6.11.0.201703011520)' severity='0'/>
      <properties size='5'>
        <property name='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.name' value='TestNG'/>
        <property name='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.description' value='TestNG plug-in for Eclipse.'/>
        <property name='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.description.url' value='http://testng.org'/>
        <property name='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.provider' value='Cedric Beust'/>
        <property name='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.type.group' value='true'/>
      </properties>
      <provides size='1'>
        <provided namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.iu' name='org.testng.eclipse.feature.group' version='6.11.0.201703011520'/>
      </provides>
      <requires size='2'>
        <required namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.iu' name='org.testng.eclipse' range='[6.11.0.201703011520,6.11.0.201703011520]'/>
        <required namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.iu' name='org.testng.eclipse.feature.jar' range='[6.11.0.201703011520,6.11.0.201703011520]'>
          <filter>
            (org.eclipse.update.install.features=true)
          </filter>
        </required>
      </requires>
      <touchpoint id='null' version='0.0.0'/>
      <licenses size='1'>
        <license uri='http://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0.html' url='http://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0.html'>
          Apache License&#xA;Version 2.0, January 2004&#xA;http://www.apache.org/licenses/&#xA;TERMS AND CONDITIONS FOR USE, REPRODUCTION, AND DISTRIBUTION&#xA;1. Definitions.&#xA;&quot;License&quot; shall mean the terms and conditions for use, reproduction,&#xA;and distribution as defined by Sections 1 through 9 of this document.&#xA;&quot;Licensor&quot; shall mean the copyright owner or entity authorized&#xA;by the copyright owner that is granting the License.&#xA;&quot;Legal Entity&quot; shall mean the union of the acting entity and&#xA;all other entities that control, are controlled by, or are under&#xA;common control with that entity. For the purposes of this definition,&#xA;&quot;control&quot; means (i) the power, direct or indirect, to cause the&#xA;direction or management of such entity, whether by contract or&#xA;otherwise, or (ii) ownership of fifty percent (50%) or more of&#xA;the outstanding shares, or (iii) beneficial ownership of such&#xA;entity.&#xA;&quot;You&quot; (or &quot;Your&quot;) shall mean an individual or Legal Entity exercising&#xA;permissions granted by this License.&#xA;&quot;Source&quot; form shall mean the preferred form for making modifications,&#xA;including but not limited to software source code, documentation&#xA;source, and configuration files.&#xA;&quot;Object&quot; form shall mean any form resulting from mechanical transformation&#xA;or translation of a Source form, including but not limited to&#xA;compiled object code, generated documentation, and conversions&#xA;to other media types.&#xA;&quot;Work&quot; shall mean the work of authorship, whether in Source or&#xA;Object form, made available under the License, as indicated by&#xA;a copyright notice that is included in or attached to the work&#xA;(an example is provided in the Appendix below).&#xA;&quot;Derivative Works&quot; shall mean any work, whether in Source or&#xA;Object form, that is based on (or derived from) the Work and&#xA;for which the editorial revisions, annotations, elaborations,&#xA;or other modifications represent, as a whole, an original work&#xA;of authorship. For the purposes of this License, Derivative Works&#xA;shall not include works that remain separable from, or merely&#xA;link (or bind by name) to the interfaces of, the Work and Derivative&#xA;Works thereof.&#xA;&quot;Contribution&quot; shall mean any work of authorship, including the&#xA;original version of the Work and any modifications or additions&#xA;to that Work or Derivative Works thereof, that is intentionally&#xA;submitted to Licensor for inclusion in the Work by the copyright&#xA;owner or by an individual or Legal Entity authorized to submit&#xA;on behalf of the copyright owner. For the purposes of this definition,&#xA;&quot;submitted&quot; means any form of electronic, verbal, or written&#xA;communication sent to the Licensor or its representatives, including&#xA;but not limited to communication on electronic mailing lists,&#xA;source code control systems, and issue tracking systems that&#xA;are managed by, or on behalf of, the Licensor for the purpose&#xA;of discussing and improving the Work, but excluding communication&#xA;that is conspicuously marked or otherwise designated in writing&#xA;by the copyright owner as &quot;Not a Contribution.&quot;&#xA;&quot;Contributor&quot; shall mean Licensor and any individual or Legal&#xA;Entity on behalf of whom a Contribution has been received by&#xA;Licensor and subsequently incorporated within the Work.&#xA;2. Grant of Copyright License. Subject to the terms and conditions&#xA;of this License, each Contributor hereby grants to You a perpetual,&#xA;worldwide, non-exclusive, no-charge, royalty-free, irrevocable&#xA;copyright license to reproduce, prepare Derivative Works of,&#xA;publicly display, publicly perform, sublicense, and distribute&#xA;the Work and such Derivative Works in Source or Object form.&#xA;3. Grant of Patent License. Subject to the terms and conditions&#xA;of this License, each Contributor hereby grants to You a perpetual,&#xA;worldwide, non-exclusive, no-charge, royalty-free, irrevocable&#xA;(except as stated in this section) patent license to make, have&#xA;made, use, offer to sell, sell, import, and otherwise transfer&#xA;the Work, where such license applies only to those patent claims&#xA;licensable by such Contributor that are necessarily infringed&#xA;by their Contribution(s) alone or by combination of their Contribution(s)&#xA;with the Work to which such Contribution(s) was submitted. If&#xA;You institute patent litigation against any entity (including&#xA;a cross-claim or counterclaim in a lawsuit) alleging that the&#xA;Work or a Contribution incorporated within the Work constitutes&#xA;direct or contributory patent infringement, then any patent licenses&#xA;granted to You under this License for that Work shall terminate&#xA;as of the date such litigation is filed.&#xA;4. Redistribution. You may reproduce and distribute copies of&#xA;the Work or Derivative Works thereof in any medium, with or without&#xA;modifications, and in Source or Object form, provided that You&#xA;meet the following conditions:&#xA;1. You must give any other recipients of the Work or Derivative&#xA;Works a copy of this License; and&#xA;2. You must cause any modified files to carry prominent notices&#xA;stating that You changed the files; and&#xA;3. You must retain, in the Source form of any Derivative Works&#xA;that You distribute, all copyright, patent, trademark, and attribution&#xA;notices from the Source form of the Work, excluding those notices&#xA;that do not pertain to any part of the Derivative Works; and&#xA;4. If the Work includes a &quot;NOTICE&quot; text file as part of its distribution,&#xA;then any Derivative Works that You distribute must include a&#xA;readable copy of the attribution notices contained within such&#xA;NOTICE file, excluding those notices that do not pertain to any&#xA;part of the Derivative Works, in at least one of the following&#xA;places: within a NOTICE text file distributed as part of the&#xA;Derivative Works; within the Source form or documentation, if&#xA;provided along with the Derivative Works; or, within a display&#xA;generated by the Derivative Works, if and wherever such third-party&#xA;notices normally appear. The contents of the NOTICE file are&#xA;for informational purposes only and do not modify the License.&#xA;You may add Your own attribution notices within Derivative Works&#xA;that You distribute, alongside or as an addendum to the NOTICE&#xA;text from the Work, provided that such additional attribution&#xA;notices cannot be construed as modifying the License.&#xA;You may add Your own copyright statement to Your modifications&#xA;and may provide additional or different license terms and conditions&#xA;for use, reproduction, or distribution of Your modifications,&#xA;or for any such Derivative Works as a whole, provided Your use,&#xA;reproduction, and distribution of the Work otherwise complies&#xA;with the conditions stated in this License.&#xA;5. Submission of Contributions. Unless You explicitly state otherwise,&#xA;any Contribution intentionally submitted for inclusion in the&#xA;Work by You to the Licensor shall be under the terms and conditions&#xA;of this License, without any additional terms or conditions.&#xA;Notwithstanding the above, nothing herein shall supersede or&#xA;modify the terms of any separate license agreement you may have&#xA;executed with Licensor regarding such Contributions.&#xA;6. Trademarks. This License does not grant permission to use&#xA;the trade names, trademarks, service marks, or product names&#xA;of the Licensor, except as required for reasonable and customary&#xA;use in describing the origin of the Work and reproducing the&#xA;content of the NOTICE file.&#xA;7. Disclaimer of Warranty. Unless required by applicable law&#xA;or agreed to in writing, Licensor provides the Work (and each&#xA;Contributor provides its Contributions) on an &quot;AS IS&quot; BASIS,&#xA;WITHOUT WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF ANY KIND, either express&#xA;or implied, including, without limitation, any warranties or&#xA;conditions of TITLE, NON-INFRINGEMENT, MERCHANTABILITY, or FITNESS&#xA;FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE. You are solely responsible for determining&#xA;the appropriateness of using or redistributing the Work and assume&#xA;any risks associated with Your exercise of permissions under&#xA;this License.&#xA;8. Limitation of Liability. In no event and under no legal theory,&#xA;whether in tort (including negligence), contract, or otherwise,&#xA;unless required by applicable law (such as deliberate and grossly&#xA;negligent acts) or agreed to in writing, shall any Contributor&#xA;be liable to You for damages, including any direct, indirect,&#xA;special, incidental, or consequential damages of any character&#xA;arising as a result of this License or out of the use or inability&#xA;to use the Work (including but not limited to damages for loss&#xA;of goodwill, work stoppage, computer failure or malfunction,&#xA;or any and all other commercial damages or losses), even if such&#xA;Contributor has been advised of the possibility of such damages.&#xA;9. Accepting Warranty or Additional Liability. While redistributing&#xA;the Work or Derivative Works thereof, You may choose to offer,&#xA;and charge a fee for, acceptance of support, warranty, indemnity,&#xA;or other liability obligations and/or rights consistent with&#xA;this License. However, in accepting such obligations, You may&#xA;act only on Your own behalf and on Your sole responsibility,&#xA;not on behalf of any other Contributor, and only if You agree&#xA;to indemnify, defend, and hold each Contributor harmless for&#xA;any liability incurred by, or claims asserted against, such Contributor&#xA;by reason of your accepting any such warranty or additional liability.&#xA;END OF TERMS AND CONDITIONS
        </license>
      </licenses>
      <copyright uri='http://beust.com' url='http://beust.com'>
        Copyright 2004-2016 Cedric Beust.
      </copyright>
    </unit>
    <unit id='org.testng.eclipse.maven.feature.feature.jar' version='6.11.0.201703011520'>
      <properties size='6'>
        <property name='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.name' value='%feature.name'/>
        <property name='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.description' value='TestNG plug-in with M2E integration for Eclipse.'/>
        <property name='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.description.url' value='http://testng.org'/>
        <property name='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.provider' value='%feature.provider'/>
        <property name='df_LT.feature.provider' value='TestNG Team'/>
        <property name='df_LT.feature.name' value='TestNG M2E Integration (Optional)'/>
      </properties>
      <provides size='3'>
        <provided namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.iu' name='org.testng.eclipse.maven.feature.feature.jar' version='6.11.0.201703011520'/>
        <provided namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.eclipse.type' name='feature' version='1.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='org.eclipse.update.feature' name='org.testng.eclipse.maven.feature' version='6.11.0.201703011520'/>
      </provides>
      <filter>
        (org.eclipse.update.install.features=true)
      </filter>
      <artifacts size='1'>
        <artifact classifier='org.eclipse.update.feature' id='org.testng.eclipse.maven.feature' version='6.11.0.201703011520'/>
      </artifacts>
      <touchpoint id='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.osgi' version='1.0.0'/>
      <touchpointData size='1'>
        <instructions size='1'>
          <instruction key='zipped'>
            true
          </instruction>
        </instructions>
      </touchpointData>
      <licenses size='1'>
        <license uri='http://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0.html' url='http://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0.html'>
          Apache License&#xA;Version 2.0, January 2004&#xA;http://www.apache.org/licenses/&#xA;TERMS AND CONDITIONS FOR USE, REPRODUCTION, AND DISTRIBUTION&#xA;1. Definitions.&#xA;&quot;License&quot; shall mean the terms and conditions for use, reproduction,&#xA;and distribution as defined by Sections 1 through 9 of this document.&#xA;&quot;Licensor&quot; shall mean the copyright owner or entity authorized&#xA;by the copyright owner that is granting the License.&#xA;&quot;Legal Entity&quot; shall mean the union of the acting entity and&#xA;all other entities that control, are controlled by, or are under&#xA;common control with that entity. For the purposes of this definition,&#xA;&quot;control&quot; means (i) the power, direct or indirect, to cause the&#xA;direction or management of such entity, whether by contract or&#xA;otherwise, or (ii) ownership of fifty percent (50%) or more of&#xA;the outstanding shares, or (iii) beneficial ownership of such&#xA;entity.&#xA;&quot;You&quot; (or &quot;Your&quot;) shall mean an individual or Legal Entity exercising&#xA;permissions granted by this License.&#xA;&quot;Source&quot; form shall mean the preferred form for making modifications,&#xA;including but not limited to software source code, documentation&#xA;source, and configuration files.&#xA;&quot;Object&quot; form shall mean any form resulting from mechanical transformation&#xA;or translation of a Source form, including but not limited to&#xA;compiled object code, generated documentation, and conversions&#xA;to other media types.&#xA;&quot;Work&quot; shall mean the work of authorship, whether in Source or&#xA;Object form, made available under the License, as indicated by&#xA;a copyright notice that is included in or attached to the work&#xA;(an example is provided in the Appendix below).&#xA;&quot;Derivative Works&quot; shall mean any work, whether in Source or&#xA;Object form, that is based on (or derived from) the Work and&#xA;for which the editorial revisions, annotations, elaborations,&#xA;or other modifications represent, as a whole, an original work&#xA;of authorship. For the purposes of this License, Derivative Works&#xA;shall not include works that remain separable from, or merely&#xA;link (or bind by name) to the interfaces of, the Work and Derivative&#xA;Works thereof.&#xA;&quot;Contribution&quot; shall mean any work of authorship, including the&#xA;original version of the Work and any modifications or additions&#xA;to that Work or Derivative Works thereof, that is intentionally&#xA;submitted to Licensor for inclusion in the Work by the copyright&#xA;owner or by an individual or Legal Entity authorized to submit&#xA;on behalf of the copyright owner. For the purposes of this definition,&#xA;&quot;submitted&quot; means any form of electronic, verbal, or written&#xA;communication sent to the Licensor or its representatives, including&#xA;but not limited to communication on electronic mailing lists,&#xA;source code control systems, and issue tracking systems that&#xA;are managed by, or on behalf of, the Licensor for the purpose&#xA;of discussing and improving the Work, but excluding communication&#xA;that is conspicuously marked or otherwise designated in writing&#xA;by the copyright owner as &quot;Not a Contribution.&quot;&#xA;&quot;Contributor&quot; shall mean Licensor and any individual or Legal&#xA;Entity on behalf of whom a Contribution has been received by&#xA;Licensor and subsequently incorporated within the Work.&#xA;2. Grant of Copyright License. Subject to the terms and conditions&#xA;of this License, each Contributor hereby grants to You a perpetual,&#xA;worldwide, non-exclusive, no-charge, royalty-free, irrevocable&#xA;copyright license to reproduce, prepare Derivative Works of,&#xA;publicly display, publicly perform, sublicense, and distribute&#xA;the Work and such Derivative Works in Source or Object form.&#xA;3. Grant of Patent License. Subject to the terms and conditions&#xA;of this License, each Contributor hereby grants to You a perpetual,&#xA;worldwide, non-exclusive, no-charge, royalty-free, irrevocable&#xA;(except as stated in this section) patent license to make, have&#xA;made, use, offer to sell, sell, import, and otherwise transfer&#xA;the Work, where such license applies only to those patent claims&#xA;licensable by such Contributor that are necessarily infringed&#xA;by their Contribution(s) alone or by combination of their Contribution(s)&#xA;with the Work to which such Contribution(s) was submitted. If&#xA;You institute patent litigation against any entity (including&#xA;a cross-claim or counterclaim in a lawsuit) alleging that the&#xA;Work or a Contribution incorporated within the Work constitutes&#xA;direct or contributory patent infringement, then any patent licenses&#xA;granted to You under this License for that Work shall terminate&#xA;as of the date such litigation is filed.&#xA;4. Redistribution. You may reproduce and distribute copies of&#xA;the Work or Derivative Works thereof in any medium, with or without&#xA;modifications, and in Source or Object form, provided that You&#xA;meet the following conditions:&#xA;1. You must give any other recipients of the Work or Derivative&#xA;Works a copy of this License; and&#xA;2. You must cause any modified files to carry prominent notices&#xA;stating that You changed the files; and&#xA;3. You must retain, in the Source form of any Derivative Works&#xA;that You distribute, all copyright, patent, trademark, and attribution&#xA;notices from the Source form of the Work, excluding those notices&#xA;that do not pertain to any part of the Derivative Works; and&#xA;4. If the Work includes a &quot;NOTICE&quot; text file as part of its distribution,&#xA;then any Derivative Works that You distribute must include a&#xA;readable copy of the attribution notices contained within such&#xA;NOTICE file, excluding those notices that do not pertain to any&#xA;part of the Derivative Works, in at least one of the following&#xA;places: within a NOTICE text file distributed as part of the&#xA;Derivative Works; within the Source form or documentation, if&#xA;provided along with the Derivative Works; or, within a display&#xA;generated by the Derivative Works, if and wherever such third-party&#xA;notices normally appear. The contents of the NOTICE file are&#xA;for informational purposes only and do not modify the License.&#xA;You may add Your own attribution notices within Derivative Works&#xA;that You distribute, alongside or as an addendum to the NOTICE&#xA;text from the Work, provided that such additional attribution&#xA;notices cannot be construed as modifying the License.&#xA;You may add Your own copyright statement to Your modifications&#xA;and may provide additional or different license terms and conditions&#xA;for use, reproduction, or distribution of Your modifications,&#xA;or for any such Derivative Works as a whole, provided Your use,&#xA;reproduction, and distribution of the Work otherwise complies&#xA;with the conditions stated in this License.&#xA;5. Submission of Contributions. Unless You explicitly state otherwise,&#xA;any Contribution intentionally submitted for inclusion in the&#xA;Work by You to the Licensor shall be under the terms and conditions&#xA;of this License, without any additional terms or conditions.&#xA;Notwithstanding the above, nothing herein shall supersede or&#xA;modify the terms of any separate license agreement you may have&#xA;executed with Licensor regarding such Contributions.&#xA;6. Trademarks. This License does not grant permission to use&#xA;the trade names, trademarks, service marks, or product names&#xA;of the Licensor, except as required for reasonable and customary&#xA;use in describing the origin of the Work and reproducing the&#xA;content of the NOTICE file.&#xA;7. Disclaimer of Warranty. Unless required by applicable law&#xA;or agreed to in writing, Licensor provides the Work (and each&#xA;Contributor provides its Contributions) on an &quot;AS IS&quot; BASIS,&#xA;WITHOUT WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF ANY KIND, either express&#xA;or implied, including, without limitation, any warranties or&#xA;conditions of TITLE, NON-INFRINGEMENT, MERCHANTABILITY, or FITNESS&#xA;FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE. You are solely responsible for determining&#xA;the appropriateness of using or redistributing the Work and assume&#xA;any risks associated with Your exercise of permissions under&#xA;this License.&#xA;8. Limitation of Liability. In no event and under no legal theory,&#xA;whether in tort (including negligence), contract, or otherwise,&#xA;unless required by applicable law (such as deliberate and grossly&#xA;negligent acts) or agreed to in writing, shall any Contributor&#xA;be liable to You for damages, including any direct, indirect,&#xA;special, incidental, or consequential damages of any character&#xA;arising as a result of this License or out of the use or inability&#xA;to use the Work (including but not limited to damages for loss&#xA;of goodwill, work stoppage, computer failure or malfunction,&#xA;or any and all other commercial damages or losses), even if such&#xA;Contributor has been advised of the possibility of such damages.&#xA;9. Accepting Warranty or Additional Liability. While redistributing&#xA;the Work or Derivative Works thereof, You may choose to offer,&#xA;and charge a fee for, acceptance of support, warranty, indemnity,&#xA;or other liability obligations and/or rights consistent with&#xA;this License. However, in accepting such obligations, You may&#xA;act only on Your own behalf and on Your sole responsibility,&#xA;not on behalf of any other Contributor, and only if You agree&#xA;to indemnify, defend, and hold each Contributor harmless for&#xA;any liability incurred by, or claims asserted against, such Contributor&#xA;by reason of your accepting any such warranty or additional liability.&#xA;END OF TERMS AND CONDITIONS
        </license>
      </licenses>
      <copyright uri='http://beust.com' url='http://beust.com'>
        Copyright 2004-2016 Cedric Beust.
      </copyright>
    </unit>
    <unit id='org.testng.eclipse' version='6.11.0.201703011520' singleton='false'>
      <update id='org.testng.eclipse' range='[0.0.0,6.11.0.201703011520)' severity='0'/>
      <properties size='1'>
        <property name='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.partial.iu' value='true'/>
      </properties>
      <provides size='4'>
        <provided namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.iu' name='org.testng.eclipse' version='6.11.0.201703011520'/>
        <provided namespace='osgi.bundle' name='org.testng.eclipse' version='6.11.0.201703011520'/>
        <provided namespace='osgi.identity' name='org.testng.eclipse' version='6.11.0.201703011520'>
          <properties size='1'>
            <property name='type' value='osgi.bundle'/>
          </properties>
        </provided>
        <provided namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.eclipse.type' name='bundle' version='1.0.0'/>
      </provides>
      <artifacts size='1'>
        <artifact classifier='osgi.bundle' id='org.testng.eclipse' version='6.11.0.201703011520'/>
      </artifacts>
      <touchpoint id='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.osgi' version='1.0.0'/>
      <touchpointData size='1'>
        <instructions size='2'>
          <instruction key='zipped'>
            true
          </instruction>
          <instruction key='manifest'>
            Bundle-SymbolicName: org.testng.eclipse&#xA;Bundle-Version: 6.11.0.201703011520&#xA;
          </instruction>
        </instructions>
      </touchpointData>
    </unit>
    <unit id='org.testng.eclipse.maven.feature.feature.group' version='6.11.0.201703011520' singleton='false'>
      <update id='org.testng.eclipse.maven.feature.feature.group' range='[0.0.0,6.11.0.201703011520)' severity='0'/>
      <properties size='7'>
        <property name='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.name' value='%feature.name'/>
        <property name='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.description' value='TestNG plug-in with M2E integration for Eclipse.'/>
        <property name='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.description.url' value='http://testng.org'/>
        <property name='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.provider' value='%feature.provider'/>
        <property name='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.type.group' value='true'/>
        <property name='df_LT.feature.provider' value='TestNG Team'/>
        <property name='df_LT.feature.name' value='TestNG M2E Integration (Optional)'/>
      </properties>
      <provides size='2'>
        <provided namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.iu' name='org.testng.eclipse.maven.feature.feature.group' version='6.11.0.201703011520'/>
        <provided namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.localization' name='df_LT' version='1.0.0'/>
      </provides>
      <requires size='3'>
        <required namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.iu' name='org.testng.eclipse.feature.group' range='0.0.0'/>
        <required namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.iu' name='org.testng.eclipse.maven' range='[6.11.0.201703011520,6.11.0.201703011520]'/>
        <required namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.iu' name='org.testng.eclipse.maven.feature.feature.jar' range='[6.11.0.201703011520,6.11.0.201703011520]'>
          <filter>
            (org.eclipse.update.install.features=true)
          </filter>
        </required>
      </requires>
      <touchpoint id='null' version='0.0.0'/>
      <licenses size='1'>
        <license uri='http://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0.html' url='http://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0.html'>
          Apache License&#xA;Version 2.0, January 2004&#xA;http://www.apache.org/licenses/&#xA;TERMS AND CONDITIONS FOR USE, REPRODUCTION, AND DISTRIBUTION&#xA;1. Definitions.&#xA;&quot;License&quot; shall mean the terms and conditions for use, reproduction,&#xA;and distribution as defined by Sections 1 through 9 of this document.&#xA;&quot;Licensor&quot; shall mean the copyright owner or entity authorized&#xA;by the copyright owner that is granting the License.&#xA;&quot;Legal Entity&quot; shall mean the union of the acting entity and&#xA;all other entities that control, are controlled by, or are under&#xA;common control with that entity. For the purposes of this definition,&#xA;&quot;control&quot; means (i) the power, direct or indirect, to cause the&#xA;direction or management of such entity, whether by contract or&#xA;otherwise, or (ii) ownership of fifty percent (50%) or more of&#xA;the outstanding shares, or (iii) beneficial ownership of such&#xA;entity.&#xA;&quot;You&quot; (or &quot;Your&quot;) shall mean an individual or Legal Entity exercising&#xA;permissions granted by this License.&#xA;&quot;Source&quot; form shall mean the preferred form for making modifications,&#xA;including but not limited to software source code, documentation&#xA;source, and configuration files.&#xA;&quot;Object&quot; form shall mean any form resulting from mechanical transformation&#xA;or translation of a Source form, including but not limited to&#xA;compiled object code, generated documentation, and conversions&#xA;to other media types.&#xA;&quot;Work&quot; shall mean the work of authorship, whether in Source or&#xA;Object form, made available under the License, as indicated by&#xA;a copyright notice that is included in or attached to the work&#xA;(an example is provided in the Appendix below).&#xA;&quot;Derivative Works&quot; shall mean any work, whether in Source or&#xA;Object form, that is based on (or derived from) the Work and&#xA;for which the editorial revisions, annotations, elaborations,&#xA;or other modifications represent, as a whole, an original work&#xA;of authorship. For the purposes of this License, Derivative Works&#xA;shall not include works that remain separable from, or merely&#xA;link (or bind by name) to the interfaces of, the Work and Derivative&#xA;Works thereof.&#xA;&quot;Contribution&quot; shall mean any work of authorship, including the&#xA;original version of the Work and any modifications or additions&#xA;to that Work or Derivative Works thereof, that is intentionally&#xA;submitted to Licensor for inclusion in the Work by the copyright&#xA;owner or by an individual or Legal Entity authorized to submit&#xA;on behalf of the copyright owner. For the purposes of this definition,&#xA;&quot;submitted&quot; means any form of electronic, verbal, or written&#xA;communication sent to the Licensor or its representatives, including&#xA;but not limited to communication on electronic mailing lists,&#xA;source code control systems, and issue tracking systems that&#xA;are managed by, or on behalf of, the Licensor for the purpose&#xA;of discussing and improving the Work, but excluding communication&#xA;that is conspicuously marked or otherwise designated in writing&#xA;by the copyright owner as &quot;Not a Contribution.&quot;&#xA;&quot;Contributor&quot; shall mean Licensor and any individual or Legal&#xA;Entity on behalf of whom a Contribution has been received by&#xA;Licensor and subsequently incorporated within the Work.&#xA;2. Grant of Copyright License. Subject to the terms and conditions&#xA;of this License, each Contributor hereby grants to You a perpetual,&#xA;worldwide, non-exclusive, no-charge, royalty-free, irrevocable&#xA;copyright license to reproduce, prepare Derivative Works of,&#xA;publicly display, publicly perform, sublicense, and distribute&#xA;the Work and such Derivative Works in Source or Object form.&#xA;3. Grant of Patent License. Subject to the terms and conditions&#xA;of this License, each Contributor hereby grants to You a perpetual,&#xA;worldwide, non-exclusive, no-charge, royalty-free, irrevocable&#xA;(except as stated in this section) patent license to make, have&#xA;made, use, offer to sell, sell, import, and otherwise transfer&#xA;the Work, where such license applies only to those patent claims&#xA;licensable by such Contributor that are necessarily infringed&#xA;by their Contribution(s) alone or by combination of their Contribution(s)&#xA;with the Work to which such Contribution(s) was submitted. If&#xA;You institute patent litigation against any entity (including&#xA;a cross-claim or counterclaim in a lawsuit) alleging that the&#xA;Work or a Contribution incorporated within the Work constitutes&#xA;direct or contributory patent infringement, then any patent licenses&#xA;granted to You under this License for that Work shall terminate&#xA;as of the date such litigation is filed.&#xA;4. Redistribution. You may reproduce and distribute copies of&#xA;the Work or Derivative Works thereof in any medium, with or without&#xA;modifications, and in Source or Object form, provided that You&#xA;meet the following conditions:&#xA;1. You must give any other recipients of the Work or Derivative&#xA;Works a copy of this License; and&#xA;2. You must cause any modified files to carry prominent notices&#xA;stating that You changed the files; and&#xA;3. You must retain, in the Source form of any Derivative Works&#xA;that You distribute, all copyright, patent, trademark, and attribution&#xA;notices from the Source form of the Work, excluding those notices&#xA;that do not pertain to any part of the Derivative Works; and&#xA;4. If the Work includes a &quot;NOTICE&quot; text file as part of its distribution,&#xA;then any Derivative Works that You distribute must include a&#xA;readable copy of the attribution notices contained within such&#xA;NOTICE file, excluding those notices that do not pertain to any&#xA;part of the Derivative Works, in at least one of the following&#xA;places: within a NOTICE text file distributed as part of the&#xA;Derivative Works; within the Source form or documentation, if&#xA;provided along with the Derivative Works; or, within a display&#xA;generated by the Derivative Works, if and wherever such third-party&#xA;notices normally appear. The contents of the NOTICE file are&#xA;for informational purposes only and do not modify the License.&#xA;You may add Your own attribution notices within Derivative Works&#xA;that You distribute, alongside or as an addendum to the NOTICE&#xA;text from the Work, provided that such additional attribution&#xA;notices cannot be construed as modifying the License.&#xA;You may add Your own copyright statement to Your modifications&#xA;and may provide additional or different license terms and conditions&#xA;for use, reproduction, or distribution of Your modifications,&#xA;or for any such Derivative Works as a whole, provided Your use,&#xA;reproduction, and distribution of the Work otherwise complies&#xA;with the conditions stated in this License.&#xA;5. Submission of Contributions. Unless You explicitly state otherwise,&#xA;any Contribution intentionally submitted for inclusion in the&#xA;Work by You to the Licensor shall be under the terms and conditions&#xA;of this License, without any additional terms or conditions.&#xA;Notwithstanding the above, nothing herein shall supersede or&#xA;modify the terms of any separate license agreement you may have&#xA;executed with Licensor regarding such Contributions.&#xA;6. Trademarks. This License does not grant permission to use&#xA;the trade names, trademarks, service marks, or product names&#xA;of the Licensor, except as required for reasonable and customary&#xA;use in describing the origin of the Work and reproducing the&#xA;content of the NOTICE file.&#xA;7. Disclaimer of Warranty. Unless required by applicable law&#xA;or agreed to in writing, Licensor provides the Work (and each&#xA;Contributor provides its Contributions) on an &quot;AS IS&quot; BASIS,&#xA;WITHOUT WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF ANY KIND, either express&#xA;or implied, including, without limitation, any warranties or&#xA;conditions of TITLE, NON-INFRINGEMENT, MERCHANTABILITY, or FITNESS&#xA;FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE. You are solely responsible for determining&#xA;the appropriateness of using or redistributing the Work and assume&#xA;any risks associated with Your exercise of permissions under&#xA;this License.&#xA;8. Limitation of Liability. In no event and under no legal theory,&#xA;whether in tort (including negligence), contract, or otherwise,&#xA;unless required by applicable law (such as deliberate and grossly&#xA;negligent acts) or agreed to in writing, shall any Contributor&#xA;be liable to You for damages, including any direct, indirect,&#xA;special, incidental, or consequential damages of any character&#xA;arising as a result of this License or out of the use or inability&#xA;to use the Work (including but not limited to damages for loss&#xA;of goodwill, work stoppage, computer failure or malfunction,&#xA;or any and all other commercial damages or losses), even if such&#xA;Contributor has been advised of the possibility of such damages.&#xA;9. Accepting Warranty or Additional Liability. While redistributing&#xA;the Work or Derivative Works thereof, You may choose to offer,&#xA;and charge a fee for, acceptance of support, warranty, indemnity,&#xA;or other liability obligations and/or rights consistent with&#xA;this License. However, in accepting such obligations, You may&#xA;act only on Your own behalf and on Your sole responsibility,&#xA;not on behalf of any other Contributor, and only if You agree&#xA;to indemnify, defend, and hold each Contributor harmless for&#xA;any liability incurred by, or claims asserted against, such Contributor&#xA;by reason of your accepting any such warranty or additional liability.&#xA;END OF TERMS AND CONDITIONS
        </license>
      </licenses>
      <copyright uri='http://beust.com' url='http://beust.com'>
        Copyright 2004-2016 Cedric Beust.
      </copyright>
    </unit>
    <unit id='https://testng.org/testng-eclipse-update-site/updatesites/6.11.0.201703011520/site.xml.org.testng.eclipse' version='1.0.0.7N7g-cLFNg67E7AY7I7AAQE7'>
      <properties size='2'>
        <property name='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.name' value='TestNG'/>
        <property name='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.type.category' value='true'/>
      </properties>
      <provides size='1'>
        <provided namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.iu' name='https://testng.org/testng-eclipse-update-site/updatesites/6.11.0.201703011520/site.xml.org.testng.eclipse' version='1.0.0.7N7g-cLFNg67E7AY7I7AAQE7'/>
      </provides>
      <requires size='2'>
        <required namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.iu' name='org.testng.eclipse.feature.group' range='[6.11.0.201703011520,6.11.0.201703011520]'/>
        <required namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.iu' name='org.testng.eclipse.maven.feature.feature.group' range='[6.11.0.201703011520,6.11.0.201703011520]'/>
      </requires>
      <touchpoint id='null' version='0.0.0'/>
    </unit>
    <unit id='org.testng.eclipse.maven' version='6.11.0.201703011520' singleton='false'>
      <update id='org.testng.eclipse.maven' range='[0.0.0,6.11.0.201703011520)' severity='0'/>
      <properties size='1'>
        <property name='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.partial.iu' value='true'/>
      </properties>
      <provides size='4'>
        <provided namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.iu' name='org.testng.eclipse.maven' version='6.11.0.201703011520'/>
        <provided namespace='osgi.bundle' name='org.testng.eclipse.maven' version='6.11.0.201703011520'/>
        <provided namespace='osgi.identity' name='org.testng.eclipse.maven' version='6.11.0.201703011520'>
          <properties size='1'>
            <property name='type' value='osgi.bundle'/>
          </properties>
        </provided>
        <provided namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.eclipse.type' name='bundle' version='1.0.0'/>
      </provides>
      <artifacts size='1'>
        <artifact classifier='osgi.bundle' id='org.testng.eclipse.maven' version='6.11.0.201703011520'/>
      </artifacts>
      <touchpoint id='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.osgi' version='1.0.0'/>
      <touchpointData size='1'>
        <instructions size='1'>
          <instruction key='manifest'>
            Bundle-SymbolicName: org.testng.eclipse.maven&#xA;Bundle-Version: 6.11.0.201703011520&#xA;
          </instruction>
        </instructions>
      </touchpointData>
    </unit>
  </units>
</repository>
